#### Contact

ishan.kaushk@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ishan-kaushik-b63612188 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Python (Programming Language) Django

Object-Relational Mapping (ORM)

# Ishan Kaushik

Python Django Developer— while(!(succeed =try())); Solan, Himachal Pradesh, India

## Summary

Experienced Python Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry.

Skilled in Web Design, Object-Relational Mapping (ORM), REST API, Communication, and Web Framework. Strong engineering professional graduated from SM University

# Experience

Python Developer August 2018 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Ameotech Informatics
Python Developer
August 2018 - July 2021 (3 years)
India

### Education

Bahra University, Solan

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Science · (2016 - 2018)